// Questions - Folklore & Evermore

export const folkloreAndEvermoreQuestions = [
     {
    "question": "And if my wishes came true it would've been you",
    "answers": ["Cardigan", "Mad Woman", "The 1", "Epiphany"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "When you are young, they assume you know nothing",
    "answers": ["Betty", "Cardigan", "Exile", "Seven"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I think I've seen this film before, and I didn't like the ending",
    "answers": ["Exile", "The 1", "August", "Peace"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "And if I'm dead to you, why are you at the wake?",
    "answers": ["The 1", "Invisible String", "Hoax", "My Tears Ricochet"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You'll find me on my tallest tiptoes, spinning in my highest heels, love",
    "answers": ["August", "Mirrorball", "Exile", "Illicit Affairs"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Sweet tea in the summer cross my heart, won't tell no other ",
    "answers": ["Seven", "The 1", "Cardigan", "This is Me Trying"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "To live for the hope of it all",
    "answers": ["Mad Woman", "Epiphany", "August", "Betty"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I was so ahead of the curve, the curve became a sphere",
    "answers": ["Cardigan", "This is Me Trying", "Invisible String", "Exile"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Take the words for what they are, a dwindling, mercurial high",
    "answers": ["The 1", "My Tears Ricochet", "Seven", "Illicit Affairs"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Something wrapped all of my past mistakes in barbed wire",
    "answers": ["Illicit Affairs", "Betty", "August", "Mad Woman"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "And women like hunting witches too, doing your dirtiest work for you",
    "answers": ["This is Me Trying", "Mad Woman", "Seven", "Betty"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Just one single glimpse of relief, to make some sense of what you've seen",
    "answers": ["Hoax", "August", "Epiphany", "Exile"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "In the garden, would you trust me",
    "answers": ["Betty", "Cardigan", "Illicit Affairs", "This is Me Trying"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "The devil's in the details, but you got a friend in me",
    "answers": ["August", "Mirrorball", "Exile", "Peace"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You knew you won, so what's the point of keeping score?",
    "answers": ["The 1", "Hoax", "Invisible String", "My Tears Ricochet"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "But I come back stronger than a 90's trend ",
    "answers": ["Willow", "Cowboy Like Me", "Tolerate It", "Gold Rush"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Because I dropped your hand while dancing",
    "answers": ["Long Story Short", "Closure", "Champagne Problems", "Ivy"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I don't like that falling feels like flying 'til the bone crush ",
    "answers": ["No Body, No Crime", "Dorothea", "Coney Island", "Gold Rush"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I escaped it too, remember how you watched me leave",
    "answers": ["'Tis the Damn Season", "Long Story Short", "Marjorie", "Happiness"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Now I'm begging for footnotes in the story of your life",
    "answers": ["No Body, No Crime", "Tolerate It", "Ivy", "Long Story Short"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Good thing his mistress took out a big life insurance policy",
    "answers": ["Cowboy Like Me", "Closure", "Ivy", "No Body, No Crime"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Tell me, when did your winning smile begin to look like a smirk?",
    "answers": ["Happiness", "Coney Island", "Willow", "Champagne Problems"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "But are you still the same soul I met under the bleachers?",
    "answers": ["'Tis the Damn Season", "Dorothea", "Tolerate It", "Gold Rush"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Sorry for not making you my centerfold",
    "answers": ["Long Story Short", "Cowboy Like Me", "Coney Island", "Ivy"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Your opal eyes are all I wish to see, he wants what's only yours ",
    "answers": ["Ivy", "Gold Rush", "Champagne Problems", "Willow"],
    "correct": 0
    },
];